看東西得比較
Looking on the bright side
正向
of things
我可以跟上，只要我想
I can keep it up if I try
想著那些機會
Thinking 'bout the chances
我錯失
thought I had
以為太陽一直都在天上
thought the sun was out this whole time
你知道我是一位魔女
You know that I'm a sorceress
你想要我也能夠掌權
I can take control if you want
啥都不能取代此時
Nothing can replace this moment
啥都不能分離我們
and nothing can divide us right now
是否原諒我
Won't you forgive me
我以前的生活？
for my life before?
有好多還要做的事
There's so much still that's left to do
是眼冒金星
Am I seeing stars
他們真這樣說？
is this what they say?
我的生活
Living my life
是虛度每一天？
on the day to day?
我知道我得跟上
I know I gotta keep this up
表演繼續
The show goes on
對我施魔咒
Put a spell on me
對我施魔咒...
Put a spell on me...
對我施魔咒
Put a spell on me
對我施魔咒...
Put a spell on me...
對我施魔咒
Put a spell on me
對我施魔咒...
Put a spell on me...
對我施魔咒
Put a spell on me
對我施魔咒...
Put a spell on me...
我是個魔女
I'm a sorceress
你感覺到沒？
can't you feel me?
我沒在耍戲
I play no games
這就是我自己
this is the real me
我快要沒時間
I'm running out of time
給愛情用
to fall in love
只因我有的魔法
'Cuz the magic I've got
不過火花
is just a spark
你是否還對我畏忌？
Are you still afraid of me?
我應該不會咬人，但...
I'd say that I don't bite, but...
你知道是謠言
You know that it isn't true
他們所言
the things they say
反正我們從沒機會
We never had a chance anyway
你知道我有魔力
You know I've got magic
就說關鍵字
just say the word
看進我眼
Look in my eyes
你心是我一切
your heart is my world
你能否感到我心
Can you feel my heartbeat?
我是一切
it's on me
我是全世界
I'm the whole damn world
我不在乎
I'm carefree
而你知道我是一位魔女
And you know that I'm a sorceress
我爽我也能夠掌權
I can take control if I please
別想那些我的錯誤
Don't think about the mistakes I've made
我不可能一直忍耐這事
I can't keep on living through this
對我施魔咒
Put a spell on me
對我施魔咒...
Put a spell on me...
對我施魔咒
Put a spell on me
對我施魔咒...
Put a spell on me...
對我施魔咒
Put a spell on me
對我施魔咒...
Put a spell on me...
對我施魔咒
Put a spell on me
對我施魔咒...
Put a spell on me...
我是個魔女
I'm a sorceress
你感覺到沒？
can't you feel me?
我沒在耍戲
I play no games
這就是我自己
this is the real me
我快要沒時間
I'm running out of time
給愛情用
to fall in love
只因我有的魔法
'Cuz the magic I've got
不過火花
is just a spark